

NGUYEN MINH NHAT

Phone: 0966332224

Email: nhattv0918@gmail.com MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

CONTACT INFORMATION

Date of birth: 15/11/1994

Marital status: Single

Gender: Male

Address: Vinh Yen, Long Duc, Tra Vinh city

OBJECTIVE

Target 2018: Apply the experience and knowledge of medicine to improve the skills of the market, becoming a professional pharmacy employee, thereby bringing value to customers and improve sales of the company.

Long-term goals: Maximize the effort to complete the tasks assigned, contribute to the development of personal career, contribute to the development of the company.

SKILLS

Language: Vietnamese, English (TOEIC)

Computer: Proficient in Word, Excel, Power Point. Also learn more about Access CB, Access NC, Visual Basic,...

Other skills: Communication and relationship building, teamwork, creative thinking, persuasive negotiation, presentation, effective work.

Special skills: counseling and treatment for patients, diet advice, nutrition for everyone

EDUCATION

♦ Pham Thai Buong High School 2010 - 2012

Vo Truong Toan University

Major: Pharmacy 2012 - 2017

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Thien An clinic 2017- 2018

Pharmacy staff

Distributing and counseling drug for patients, clinical pharmacology seminars with doctors

Personal Trainer 2014 - 2018

4 years experience in the field of Gym, specializing in nutrition advice, diet and exercise

EXTRA ACTIVITIES

Thien Duyen Charity in Hau Giang province

2012 - 2017

Volunteers

Carry out volunteer journeys to bring books and warm clothes to elementary school children.

🔷 Admin page ''Tài Liệu Y Dược''

2017 - 2018

Facebook page sharing medical documents, lectures and information

Join Nutrilite Amway's "Lực sĩ đẹp" course

2018

This is a course specializing in nutrition and functional foods, sales and consulting skills of Nutrilite

INTERESTST

- Read medical books, learn about drugs, soft skills books
- Gym
- Travel